<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Feel Good Inc</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tut_content_desc">Graphic of a woman with flowers blooming from her head</string>
    <string name="tut_1_text">Welcome to Feel Good Inc.</string>
    <string name="tut_2_text">A daily mental health journaling tool</string>
    <string name="tut_3_text">Select your current mood\n\nWrite a log\n\nSee trends\nover time\n\nFeel Good!</string>
    <string name="eula_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="eula">
                Feel Good Inc. should not be viewed as a substitute for therapy or other psychological or
                psychiatric treatment, nor should they be considered a substitute for a diagnosis or
                medical advice.\n\nNotwithstanding the scientific research on journaling, Feel Good Inc. makes no representation
                or warranty that the User’s mental health will improve. Reliance on the Apps and the
                information they contain is strictly at the User’s risk. If the App licensee has been
                diagnosed with a psychiatric condition they may wish to speak to their medical
                practitioner before use.\n\nFeel Good Inc. makes no representation or warranty that the Apps will prevent, cure or treat
                diseases, disorders or conditions, including those related to cognition and the brain, but
                not limited to such.\n\nFeel Good Inc. has designed the Apps for general information purposes only. We make no
                representation or warranty regarding accuracy, completeness, suitability and safety. The
                User assumes full responsibility and Feel Good Inc. is not liable for any consequences resulting
                from reliance.\n\nThe Apps should not be viewed as a substitute for addiction or rehabilitation programmes.
                Some of the Apps are designed to increase productivity and help manage habits. Although
                the User may find them helpful in overcoming addictions, Feel Good Inc. makes no
                representation or warranty that they are fit for this purpose. The App licensee should not
                delay in obtaining such intervention as a result of usage.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="add_mood">Add mood</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="email_example">exampleuser@feelgood.com</string>
    <string name="email_tag">Email:</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="enter_new_password_tag">Enter New Password:</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an account</string>
    <string name="title_activity_signup">SignupActivity</string>

</resources>